Your
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): boss, your former boss, Secretary Noem, called them domestic terrorists. And yesterday, in front of the House and the day before here in the Senate, she refused to retract her statement, calling them domestic terrorists.
Speaker 2: So I have a very simple question for you
today.
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): Would you agree with me that Rene Good and Alex Preddy are not domestic terrorists?
And
Speaker 3: Senator, this is an issue that doesn't involve me. No, no, it does. Because you're going to be- They were shot after I left.
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): You're going to be the American ambassador of El Salvador if you're confirmed. So I have an interest in your views of the Constitution and your views about what happened in Minneapolis, which all of America has got to see because it's on video. And people were shocked, including Republicans, some of them were shocked,
that the
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): Secretary of Homeland Security refused to retract a statement calling two American citizens peacefully protesting domestic terrorists. And I'm shocked that you refuse to say today that
Speaker 4: they're not domestic terrorists. You're refusing to confirm that they're not domestic terrorists.
Speaker 5: Look, anytime somebody is shot and killed by law enforcement, serious issue. There should be a process to evaluate it in an investigation and it not be predetermined.
Speaker 5: So exactly,
Speaker 2: Mr., it should not be predetermined. So that's why I asked you whether you would agree
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): that you shouldn't just call them domestic terrorists. Let me move on. I found it astounding, I find it astounding that you can't say here at a public hearing to be ambassador
of the
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): United States to another country that these two American citizens that have been shot and killed by federal agents, that they weren't domestic terrorists. I find that astounding.